let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "   The father of mysql is ...........",
    answer: "Michael Widenius",
    options: [
        "  Bill Joy ",
        "Bill Gates",
        "Stephanie Wall",
        "Michael Widenius",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The program called mysql is ................",
    answer: "A Client Program That Lets You Send SQL Commands To The Database Engine",
    options: [
     "The Database Engine",
     "There Isn't A Program Just Called Mysql",
     "A Client Program That Lets You Send SQL Commands To The Database Engine",
    "None of Above"
      
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of these is not a valid name for a column?",
    answer: " From",
    options: [
      " Near",
      "From ",
       " Far",
      "To"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is available in mysql?",
    answer: " CREATE DATABASE",
    options: [
      " CREATE DATABASE",
      "CREATE SCHEMA",
      " CREATE TRIGGER",
     " CREATE VIEW"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " Which of the following is not supported by mysql?",
    answer: "  Stored Procedures ",
    options: [
     "  Regular Expression Matching",
"Temporary (Hash) Tables",
"Stored Procedures",
"Table Joining"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "If you want to undo a grant you should use ............",
    answer: " REVOKE",
    options: [
      " DELETE",
      " UNGRANT",
      " REVOKE",
      " UNDO"
    ]
},
{
 numb: 7, 
    question: " What kind of replication is supported by the mysql server?",
    answer:   " Master To Slave Replication ",
    options:[
      " Single File Based Clustering",
      " Master To Slave Replication ",
      "  Multiple-master Replication",
      " MySQL Doesn't Support Replication "
    ]
},

{
  numb: 8,
  question: "To use mysql on your computer you will need ?",   
  answer:   " Some Sort Of Client Program To Access The Databases",
  options:[
    " A Browser",
" FTP And Telnet",
"Perl, PHP Or Java",
" Some Sort Of Client Program To Access The Databases"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
    question: "MYSQL comes with as standard with client libraries for?",
    answer: " C Only",
    options:[
      " C Only",
      "Java And C",
      "Java Only",
      " Perl, PHP And C"
   
    ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
   question: "Which of the following is true about mysql?",
   answer: "  All of the above",
   options:[
    " Scalable",
" High Flexibility",
" Easy to use",
" All of the above"
]

},

];